find-near-me.info 2015-04-19

# Find Places Near Me Privacy Policy

Last updated April 5, 2015

## Your privacy is critically important to us. At Find Places Near Me we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We won't ask you for personal information unless we really need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services.
  * In our service, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, kept private, and permanently deleted.

It is Find Places Near Me's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please send an email to 1cafvwc@xz3s-1rm2-wn.qult.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Find Places Near Me collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Find Places Near Me's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Find Places Near Me's visitors use Find Places Near Me. From time to time, Find Places Near Me may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Find Places Near Me also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Find Places Near Me does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Find Places Near Me choose to interact with Find Places Near Me in ways that require Find Places Near Me to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Find Places Near Me gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website at Find Places Near Me to provide a birthday and email address. In each case, Find Places Near Me collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Find Places Near Me. Find Places Near Me does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Find Places Near Me may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to Find Places Near Me. For instance, Find Places Near Me may monitor the most popular pages on the Find Places Near Me site. Find Places Near Me may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Find Places Near Me does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Find Places Near Me discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Find Places Near Me's behalf or to provide services available at Find Places Near Me, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Find Places Near Me, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Find Places Near Me discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Find Places Near Me believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Find Places Near Me, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Find Places Near Me and have supplied your email address, Find Places Near Me may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Find Places Near Me and our products.

Find Places Near Me takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Find Places Near Me uses cookies to help Find Places Near Me identify and track visitors, their usage of Find Places Near Me, and their website access preferences. Find Places Near Me visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Find Places Near Me, with the drawback that certain features of Find Places Near Me may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If Find Places Near Me, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Find Places Near Me goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Find Places Near Me may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Find Places Near Me may change Find Places Near Me's Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Find Places Near Me's sole discretion. Find Places Near Me encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Acknowledgment

Find Places Near Me thanks Automattic for writing a straightforward [Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and making it available under the [Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 2.5 Generic License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/).
